- 你错了  - 我没错
- You're wrong.  - No, I'm not.
- 你就是错了  - 我没错
- Yes, you are.  - No, I'm not.
你来说 那种互联网上
Settle this. Those little animated pictures
会动的小图片 是叫"动图"还是"闪图"?
on the Internet, are they called "gifs" or "jifs"?
这里应该指的是"会动的"
Well, the G stands for "graphics."
根据意思 我说该是"动图"
That's a hard G, so I'd say "gif."
什么... 发明的那家伙说是"闪图"
W... The guy who invented it says it's "jif."
不好意思 你说的是家伙还是夹伙?
I'm sorry, do you mean the guy or the juy?
允许你们猜三次
Well, I'll give you three guesses
我干嘛这么生气
why I'm so irritated.
有事情违背了你的预想
Something happened different from the way you wanted it.
坏事还真是传千里
I guess news travels fast.
猜对了 他们选择邀请了
It's true, a select group of scientists
一批科学家去理查德·费曼故居
was invited to a weekend symposium
参加周末学术讨论会
at a former home of Richard Feynman,
我没被邀请
and I wasn't included.
Sheldon 我觉得这肯定不是因为他们认为
Oh, Sheldon, I'm sure it's not because they don't think
- 你不是出色的科学家  - 没错
- you're an elite scientist.  - Yeah,
肯定是因为你太让人蛋疼了
I bet you anything it's just 'cause you're a pain in the ass.
你就别安慰我了
You're just saying that to make me feel better.
听着 你可以花一整天
Look, you can spend the rest of the day
- 不爽这件事  - 同意
- being bitter about this.  - Agreed.
我本来还想说"或者"的 还是算了吧
I was gonna say "or," but why bother?
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第20集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 凤梨酥考砸了心很塞
校对: UU养了只狐狸叫查理
翻译: 酱油影 打肉肉君 奥利奥 凤梨酥
嘿 Raj
Hey, Raj.
嘿 我给你买了份小礼物
Hey, I got you a little gift.
好多女童子军曲奇哦
Oh, that's a lot of Girl Scout Cookies.
你懂的 我是印度人
You know me. I'm from India.
小孩一求我 我就受不了
I can't resist children begging.
房子过户的事办得怎么样了?
So, how's it going with the title to the house?
很好 都搞定了
Great, it's all done.
律师找到了我爸爸
The lawyer tracked down my father
让他签了过户文件
and got him to sign it over.
我不必见他 不用和他说话
I didn't have to meet him, I didn't have to talk to him,
都不用知道他人在哪里
I don't even know where he is.
哇哦 你完全不好奇吗?
Wow, so you're not curious at all?
不
Nope.
万一他在监狱里呢?
Hm. What if he's in prison?
万一他是个间谍呢?
What if he's a spy?
万一他是披头士翻唱乐队的呢?
What if he's in a Beatles cover band?
你看 如果他的鼻子和发型和你一样
I'm just saying, if he's got your nose and haircut,
就绝对是个翻版林戈
he'd make a killer Ringo.
林戈·斯塔尔 英国摇滚乐队"披头士"的鼓手
谢谢你愿意参与录制
Thanks again for agreeing to do this.
不客气 我从没上过播客
Oh, it's cool. I've never been on a podcast before.
那你选了个不错的开端
Well, you picked a good one to start.
Wil的播客上过很多大牌嘉宾
Wil's had lots of great guests.
乔纳森·弗雷克斯 布伦特·斯派尔
Jonathan Frakes, Brent Spiner,
米切尔·道恩 盖茨·迈克范登...
Michael Dorn, Gates McFadden...
那些都是演星际迷航的演员
Those are Star Trek people.
没错!
Yes!
我能猜对
I only figured that out
是因为我一个都没听说过
because I've never heard of any of them.
是我活该
I deserve that.
我请你上我的节目 还自己开车过来
I invited you on my show and I drove here.
抱歉
Sorry.
好 这基本上就是
Okay, so, this is basically gonna be
一个小型脱口秀
just like a little talk show.
我们会接几个观众来电
Uh, we're gonna take some calls,
然后聊聊在"杀人猿2"
we'll talk about what it was like on the set
拍摄现场的情况
of Serial Ape-ist 2.
肯定会很有趣的
It should be really fun.
- 会很令人兴奋的  - 好吧
- This is exciting.  - Yeah.
有多少人会听?
So, how many people listen?
很多人会事后下载
Most people download it later,
但一般会有几千个人在线听
but usually a few thousand people listen live.
什么?! 有几千个人
What?! A few thousand people
在线听你大聊宅男话题?
listen to you talk about nerd stuff?
再说一次 听在耳边
Again, right in the ears,
伤在心里
straight to the feelings.
你能把盐递过来吗?
Can you please pass the salt?
当然
Sure.
反正我没被邀请去理查德·费曼故居
It's not like I was invited to Richard Feynman's house
也没什么事情做
and have anything better to do.
今晚你就打算用这态度过了?
Is this how the rest of the night's going to be?
我又看不到未来
I don't know the future.
你觉得会不会有一颗
Do you think there's a chance
小行星撞上地球
that an asteroid could hit the Earth,
毁掉理查德·费曼故居和里面的所有人?
destroying Feynman's house and everyone in it?
不会 Sheldon
No, Sheldon.
那系好安全带 今晚会天摇地动的
Then buckle up, you're in for a cranky night.
你一向坚持贯彻的
According to the codicil of the Relationship Agreement
恋爱条例的附加条约里写过
which you insisted upon,
约会的时候我们不能生气或不高兴
we're not allowed to pout or be moody on date night.
要知道 我加这条是为了防范你姨妈期的情绪
You know I just put that in because of uterus stuff.
好吧 但对你也适用
Well, it applies to you, too.
我就怕你会提到这点
I was afraid you might bring this up,
所以我想了办法解决
so I have a work-around.
看吧
There you go.
正如你看到的 我在笑呢
As far as you're concerned, I'm smiling.
我必须承认 我现在是真的有点笑了
Although, I must admit, I'm smiling a little bit
因为钻俩小洞简直是天才之举
at the moment because this loophole is so brilliant.
Bernadette 你有没有想过
So, Bernadette, have you thought
要怎么重新装修这个房子?
about how you're going to redecorate this place?
嗯 我想要
You know, I'm thinking
扯掉地毯
ripping up the carpets,
可能要剥掉墙纸
maybe lose the wallpaper,
重新装照明灯...
all new light fixtures...
要知道 如果你敲掉这堵墙
You know, if you knocked out this wall,
就会有一个开放式的空间
it would give you an open floor plan,
然后... 听着有点可怕 不过会很有趣的...
and then... it's a little scary, but could be fun...
来个室内篝火
indoor fire pit.
嘿 我在这房子里长大的 懂吗?
Hey, I grew up in this house, okay?
不准砸掉任何东西
No one's knocking anything down.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
等他去漫展的时候
When he's at Comic-Con,
我就带个铁球来砸墙
I'm bringing in a wrecking ball.
有什么事?
Can I help you?
你好 你是Howard Wolowitz吗?
Hi. Are you Howard Wolowitz?
对
Yes.
这可能有点尴尬
Um, this is a little weird,
但有个律师联系了我的父亲
but a lawyer was trying to contact my father,
因为这栋房子仍旧在他的名下
because his name was still on the title for this house.
什... 什么 谁是你父亲?
W... uh, who's your father?
Sam Wolowitz啊
Sam Wolowitz.
他是我父亲啊
S-Sam Wolowitz is my father.
我知道
I know.
嗯 等等 如果我们的父亲是同一个人...
Well, wait, so if we have the same father...
那么你就是说
are you saying
你是我的同父异母的弟弟吗?
you're my half-brother?
我觉得是这样的
I think so.
Bernadette 这边的事太奇葩了!
Bernadette, weird things are happening out here!
我觉得当我看到这个剧本的电影名的时候
I think I started to suspect it was a bad movie
我就开始怀疑这是一部烂片了
when I looked at the script and saw the title,
杀人恶猿2之
Serial Ape-ist 2:
猴见猴杀
Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
剧透警告:
Uh, spoiler alert:
当猴子看到你时 它就会杀你
after the monkey sees, it kills.
给你
Psst.
我刚才接到了一个小纸条
I've just been handed a note.
我准备把它读出来
I'm going to read it.
"Wil 你还要健怡可乐吗?
"Wil, do you want more Diet Coke?
我们还有果汁哟"
Also, we have juice."
我没想打断你们来着
I-I didn't want to interrupt.
嗯 刚才那个声音
Uh, that voice you just heard
是Leonard发出来的 Penny的未婚夫
belongs to Leonard, Penny's fiancé.
Leonard 你为什么不戴个耳机加入我们呢?
Uh, Leonard, why don't you grab some headphones and join us?
- 可以吗?  - 是啊
- Really?  -  Yeah.
太棒了
Yeah, great.
那么 当Leonard准备的时候
So, while Leonard gets set up,
我们先来接个电话吧
let's take a call.
你好 这位观众 你现在接通了
Hello, caller, you are on
出演杀人恶猿2的演员Penny和Wil的电话
with Penny and Wil from Serial Ape-ist 2.
我没什么要问的
I don't have a question.
我只是想说我是这个电影的一个粉丝
I just want to say I'm a big fan of the movie.
这部电影我大概看了有10遍吧
I've seen it, like, ten times.
好吧 我对第一遍深表抱歉
Okay, well, I'll apologize for the first time,
不过剩下的那九遍可是你自己找的啊
but the other nine are on you.
非常感谢 这位观众
Thanks a lot, caller.
你知道吗 其实这部电影
You know that the movie actually
另类得挺受欢迎的
a little bit of a cult following.
- 真的吗?  - 是的
- Really?  - Yeah.
我当时在一个科幻展上
I was at a science-fiction convention
看到了一个女人打扮成了你演的那个半人半猿角色
and I saw a woman dressed as your half-ape character.
哦 如果她是
Oh, if she was
和一个穿的像一个香蕉一样的印度人在一起的话
with an Indian guy dressed like a banana,
那他们就是我的两个朋友Howard和Raj
that was just my friends, Howard and Raj.
好 现在我们来接一个特约嘉宾的电话
All right, it's time for a very special guest caller,
他是我的一个朋友 你们可能能认出
a friend of mine, who you probably know
他是Clerks电影的导演
as the director of such movies as Clerks,
或者从播客和书里
or from podcasts and books
听到看到他自卖自夸 自己就是那个
where he often reminds you that he's the guy
导演了Clerks的人
who directed Clerks.
你好 Kevin Smith
Hello, Kevin Smith.
嗨 哥们 你过得还好吧 Wil?
KEVIN: Hey, man, yo, is everything okay, Wil?
因为都过了两分钟了
'Cause it's been, like, two minutes
你还没扯到Stand By Me这部你的成名电影
and you haven't even brought up Stand By Me.
嗨 Kevin!
Hey, Kevin!
和你说话我好激动啊
It's really exciting to talk to you.
真心的
It really is.
啊 你们嘴太甜了 所以 Penny 听好了
Oh, you guys are very sweet. So, Penny, listen,
我看过你的电影了
I saw your movie.
哇哦 这么烂我也不想的
Oh, wow. I wish it was better.
哦 别担心
Oh, don't worry about it.
你看过Kevin的电影吗?
Have you seen some of Kevin's films?
你在找打吗 Wheaton
You're cruisin' for a beatin', Wheaton.
好了 我挺喜欢这部电影 Penny
Anyway, man, I dug the ape movie, Penny.
我觉得你演的非常好
And I thought you were, like, really great in it.
天哪
Aw.
你知道吗 我也在这部电影里呢
You know, I'm in the movie, too.
是又怎么样 Penny!
Yeah, whatever. Penny!
Penny 你怎么不多拍点电影?
Penny, how come you're not in more stuff, man?
我现在就想让你试镜了
I'd cast you in a minute.
- 真的吗?  - 是啊
- Seriously?  - Oh, yeah, man.
我现在正在准备一部电影的前期工作
I'm actually in pre-production on a movie right now.
它和我之前
Way different
做的大不一样
than anything I've ever done before.
这部电影叫Clerks三
It's called Clerks 3.
你应该过来
You should come over
试着演一段
and read for a part.
哦 天哪 太好了
Oh, my, I would love that.
你已经有了新工作了啊
You have a new job.
我可以兼职啊
Well, maybe I can do both.
我觉得你不行
I don't think you can do both.
我好像没问你意见吧
I don't think I asked you.
嗯 告诉他 Penny
Yeah, you tell him, Penny.
关你什么事 Kevin Smith
Stay out of it, Kevin Smith.
你觉得人会活到某个岁数之后
Do you think there comes a point in life
被忽视也觉得不难过吗?
when it stops feeling bad to be left out of things?
可能不会吧
Probably not.
融入社交活动
It's an evolutionary advantage
对进化是有好处的啊
to be included in group activities.
你知道吗?
You know what?
我曾经是进化论的粉丝
I used to be a fan of evolution
但是我已经完全进化完了
but I've since evolved,
所以现在 我觉得挺蠢的
and now I think it's dumb.
被忽视是一种糟糕的感觉
Being left out is a terrible feeling.
没人比我更了解这种感受
No one understands that better than I do.
嘿 看看你
Hey, look at that.
你在你自己举的例子里面都是一个人
Even in your example, you're all by yourself.
当我们学校爆发虱子传染病时
When there was a lice epidemic at my school
除了我之外别人都得了
everybody got it except me.
我在我头发上撒糖 想蒙骗大家
I tried to fool everyone by sprinking sugar in my hair,
但是我却被蜜蜂蛰了
but I just got attacked by bees.
我脑子里都有画面了
I can just picture them all right now
他们在费曼故居
at Feynman's house
讨论着薛定谔
probably discussing Schrodinger
同时
and at the same time
这里借用了"薛定谔的猫"的梗
也没有讨论薛定谔
not discussing Schrodinger.
对吧?
See?
他们错过了这样搞笑的笑话
They're missing out on hilarious jokes like that.
同时也没错过
And at the same time, not.
又让我回想起小时候 我那傻哥傻姐
It reminds me of when my stupid brother and sister
俩人在客厅建床单堡垒
would build forts in the living room
还不让我进去
and wouldn't let me in.
我太讨厌那种感觉了
I hated that so much.
虽说
You know,
我不能帮你
there's nothing I can do
得到研讨会的邀请
about getting you invited to the symposium,
但如果你愿意...
but if you wanted...
我们可以建一个堡垒
we could build a fort.
这会不会太幼稚?
Isn't that a little juvenile?
比这还幼稚吗?
More juvenile than this?
我去拿毯子
I'll get the blankets.
你去谷歌一下 怎么才能像小孩一样玩得欢
You Google how to have childlike fun.
看来我有点招待不周
You know what, I'm being a bad host.
我再去拿一些咖啡
Let me get some more coffee.
- 让我来 Howard  - 不用了 我可以
- Oh, let me do it, Howard.  - No, I got it.
Josh 你是做什么的?
So, Josh, what do you do?
我在圣地亚哥修读海洋学
I'm studying oceanography down in San Diego.
真不错
Oh, how nice.
我喜欢"海底总动员"
I loved Finding Nemo.
闲话少说
Enough chitchat.
我们怎么知道你说的是真的?
How do we know you are who you say you are?
我为什么要骗人?
Why would I lie?
好吧 你难住我了
Okay, you got me there.
- 你来这是要借钱吗?  - 不
- You here looking for money?  - No.
那是要他的肾 眼角膜 还是肝吗?
A kidney, cornea, piece of his liver?
不
No.
那你有一支披头士翻唱乐队
You're in a Beatles cover band
想让Howard代替你爸当林戈
and you need Howard to replace your dad as Ringo.
你去看看咖啡怎么样了吧?
Why don't you help with the coffee?
好的 但有东西不对劲(有鱼腥味)
Okay, but something smells fishy.
不单单是因为
And not just because
你研究海底生物的缘故
you work around sea animals.
其实海洋学还挺有意思的
That actually sounds interesting,
有机会我想多了解一些
and I'd like to learn more about it.
嘿 你没事吧?
Hey, you okay?
有事
Not really.
这家伙凭空出现
This guy shows up out of the blue,
我突然间有弟弟了?
and now I have a brother?
我爸还成了另一个家?
My father has another family?
我能理解
I get it.
你打算怎么办?
What do you want to do?
我不知道 我...
I don't know. I...
我只想让他离开
I'd just like him to go away.
我还没准备好
I can't deal with this.
好吧 我帮你解决
All right, I've got your back.
谢谢你 走吧
Thank you. Come on.
顺便说一句
And I'd like to point out
这墙真是保护隐私的利器!
this wall just provided a lot of privacy!
我哥竟然是个宇航员
I can't believe my brother's an astronaut.
- 真不可思议 那是什么体验?  - 听着 小伙子
- That's amazing.  What was it like?  - Listen, dude,
你是时候该离开了
it's time for you to hit the road.
嘿 这年轻人问了个好问题
Hey, hey, the young man asked a good question.
刚转频道的听众朋友
So, for those of you just tuning in,
您正在收听
we are listening
- 我的搭档和他未婚夫在吵...  - 不不不
- to a really fun fight between my costar...  - No, no, no.
我们没在吵架 我们只是在...
We're not fighting; we're just...
交流
having a conversation.
好吧
All right.
您正在收听我在杀人猿2中的搭档演员
We're listening to a really fun conversation
和他未婚夫之间有趣的"交流"
between my costar from Serial Ape-ist 2
而在他看来
and her fiancé, who doesn't believe
女人不该有梦想
women should have dreams.
把果汁还给我
Give me back that juice.
我试下镜有何妨?
What is the harm if I audition?
可万一你试成了呢?
Well, what if you get it?
我不知道 或许拍个电影
I don't know, I make a movie,
然后名利双收
become rich and famous,
赢个奥斯卡 金球奖
win an Oscar, a Golden Globe
过上无比幸福的生活
and live an incredibly wonderful life.
就靠Kevin Smith的电影?
From a Kevin Smith movie?
我要挂了
Oh, I'm hanging up now.
别听他说 伙计
Don't you listen to him, buddy.
你很棒
You're awesome.
你是史上最佳导演之一
You're one of the greatest directors of our time.
我这没你的戏份 Wheaton
I don't have a part for you, Wheaton.
跟Kevin Smith的通话就到这里
And that was Kevin Smith.
多谢你啊
Thanks a lot.
我只是在保护你
I'm just trying to protect you.
我多少次看见你为了演员梦
How many times did I see you get your heart broken
到头来心碎不已?
trying to make it as an actress?
与其保护我 你何不试着
Okay, instead of protecting me, why don't you try
在我遇到好事时表现得激动点?
being excited when something good happens?
我一直很为你激动啊!
I'm always excited for you!
你找到新工作 我很激动的
I'm excited that you found this new job
而且你的工资也不低
where you're making decent money.
不低? 我赚的钱可是你的两倍
Decent? I make twice what you make.
等等 两倍?!
Wait, twice?!
是啊
Yeah.
就是 "乘以二"的两倍
Like, "times two" twice?
在家收听的听众朋友 Leonard刚发现
For those of you at home, Leonard just found out
他未婚妻赚的钱完爆了他自己
his fiancée makes way more money than he does.
咱们接着听
Let's listen.
我上了半辈子的学
I went to school for half my life.
考取了博士学位
I have a doctorate.
可现在还在偿还助学贷款
I'm still paying off college loans.
你还欠多少?
Well, how much do you owe?
或许我能帮着还一点
Maybe I can help you out.
Wil 可以先暂停一下广播吗?
Wil, can we just turn off the podcast for a little bit?
在家的听众朋友
For those of you at home,
我在摇头说不
I am shaking my head "no."
弄得怎么样了 Sheldon?
How's it going, Sheldon?
棒极了!
Wonderful!
我刚把彩灯挂上
I just finished hanging the lights.
我能进来吗?
Can I come in?
当然 不过要从侧面进来
Yes, oh, but enter through the side.
蝙蝠侠是载重的毯子
Batman is a load-bearing blanket.
好棒啊
Amazing.
我知道
I know.
这可不是打印出来的
This isn't the printout.
这是我的真脸
This is my real face.
我们愣着干嘛?
What are we doing?
这是个堡垒
This is a fort.
坐地上吧
Let's sit on the floor.
过苦日子? 好吧
Roughing it? Okay.
这样子看一切都显得好大
Everything looks so big from down here.
原来当Leonard是这种感觉
This must be how Leonard feels.
我有点意外你耳朵里
I'm surprised you could hear me
有片薄荷糖 你还听得见!
with this Thin Mint in your ear!
很厉害吧?
Yeah, pretty cool, huh?
是啊
Yeah.
总之 我差不多该走了
Anyway, I should probably get going.
Howie 你有没有发现你每次变魔术之后
Howie, have you noticed how often
人们的反应都是这样?
people say that when you start to do magic?
不好意思 我还要开好久的车回去
Sorry, I have a long drive.
好吧 有机会再见
Well, I hope I get to see you again.
好啊
I hope so, too.
我一直梦想着能有个兄弟和我一起玩传球游戏呢
I've always dreamed of having a brother to play catch with.
接着做梦吧
Keep dreaming.
嘿 我在一次洛杉矶队的棒球比赛上
Hey, I threw out the first pitch
- 投了第一个球呢  - 哇
- at an Angels game.  - Wow.
他和机器人做的
He did it with a robot.
你和机器人睡了?
You had sex with a robot?
她不是这个意思
That's not what she meant.
不过从技术层面上来说 他确实睡过
But technically, yes.
等等 如果你挣了这么多钱
Hang on, if you're making all this money,
你都用来做什么了?
where is it?
存在安全的地方了
In a safe place.
什么意思 你放在床底下了?
What does that mean, under your bed?
不是啊
No, it means
我投到好几种不同的股票和债券里了
a diversified portfolio of stocks and bonds.
我不是那种保守的人
I'm not overly conservative.
我还年轻 我的顾问说我可以冒点风险
I'm young, so my guy said I can afford to take some risks.
等下 你还有"顾问"?
Wait a minute, you have "a guy"?
你没有吗?
Don't you have a guy?
我怎么会有理财顾问? 我连财都没有!
Why would I have a guy? I don't have any money!
哦 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie,
你真的应该去多挣点钱
you should really get some money.
正在收听直播的朋友们
For those of you listening at home,
这期节目是不是很精彩?
how great is this?
Wil 我拜托你先别录了行吗
Wil, I'm begging you, just please turn that off.
没问题
Sure.
欢迎回来
And we're back.
Leonard 这件事有这么重要吗?
Leonard, why are you making such a big deal out of this?
这几年 我们之间的角色确实发生了一些变化
So our roles have changed a bit over the last couple years.
可生活就是这样的啊
This is the way life is.
而且我相信 我们的生活还会继续变化的
And I'm sure in time they'll change again.
真棒 现在你不光比我更事业有成
Great, you're not only more successful than me,
还比我更成熟懂事了
now you're more mature.
好吧 如果有一天我不去上班
Okay, look, would it make you feel better
而是愚蠢地去参加Kevin Smith的电影的试镜
if I did something dumb like sneak out of work one day
你会不会感觉好一点?
to go audition for a Kevin Smith movie?
那就太好了 谢了!
That would be great, thank you!
我想插一句
I'm just gonna jump in here real quick.
Leonard 就在刚才
Leonard, a moment ago,
你还死都不愿意让Penny继续她的演艺事业
you were dead set against Penny resuming her acting career,
可现在你却全力支持
but now you're all for it.
这是不是说明 她把你当猴耍?
Is it fair to say that she played you like a violin?
确实是 Wil
Yes, it is, Wil.
我真的好想知道
So, I have to ask,
那个机器人性感吗?
was the robot sexy?
其实吧
It was actually
那就是一条机械手臂而已
just a mechanical hand.
因为有机械手臂就够了 对吧?
Because that's all you need, right?
你真是我亲弟弟
You are my brother.
第一届城堡联赛
Okay, so the final four forts
也可以说是第一届"堡赛"的
in the first annual best fort ever contest,
四强选手分别是...
or "fort off," are...
诺克斯堡 (美国用于储备黄金的堡垒)
Fort Knox,
提康德罗加堡 (美国纽约州北部大型堡垒)
Fort Ticonderoga,
萨姆特堡 (美国一处石质防御工程) 以及...
Fort Sumter and...
舒服毯子堡
Fort Cozy McBlanket.
我觉得...
I'd say...
诺克斯堡比提康德罗加堡要好
Knox over Ticonderoga
因为那里面有美联储的金库
because it's got the gold.
同意 而舒服毯子堡比萨姆特堡要好
Mm-hmm. And McBlanket over Sumter
因为它针数更多 更严密保暖
because it has a higher thread count.
诶
Oh.
十点了
10:00.
约会夜结束
Date night's over.
等等 别走
Wait, no.
我们还没选出冠军呢
We haven't picked a winner.
我们都知道谁会获胜啊
We both know this one's gonna win.
那倒是
Well, of course we do.
诺克斯堡可没有
Fort Knox doesn't have a secret
秘密物理图书馆
physics lending library.
好啦 我帮你收拾一下这里
Come on, I'll help you take this down.
等会
Well, wait.
如果 这一次
What if, just this once,
我们延长约会夜的时间长度
we suspend the date night parameters
你在这里多待一会 怎么样?
and you stay later?
只要我们都同意延长时间
Well, as long as we're suspending the parameters,
我可以待到很晚
I could stay really late
并且把今晚发展成第一次在你家过夜
and we could have our first sleepover.
这可是一大步啊
That's a big step.
这个城堡也不小
It's a big fort.
好吧
Very well.
我同意 今晚将是一次非限制级的
I will agree to a family-friendly,
女生在男生家里的过夜
G-rated, boy-girl sleepover.
是PG级 (须有家长指导观看)
PG.
有些场面可能会少儿不宜
Some scenes may be too intense for younger viewers.
还是非限制级吧
G-rated,
不过可能不适宜婴幼儿观看
with a warning for families with babies and toddlers.
就这么决定了
You got yourself a sleepover.
你需要去借牙刷
Do you need to borrow
或者睡衣吗?
a toothbrush or pajamas?
要是你知道
Would it alarm you to know
我两年前就在你家藏起来这些东西以防万一
that I hid those things here two years ago
你会觉得后怕吗?
just in case this ever came up?
当然会
It would,
不过你知道我最喜欢有备无患了
but you know how much I admire preparedness.
你怎么知道我们会在客厅?
How did you know we'd be in the living room?
谁告诉你我只藏了一套了?
Who says this is the only one I hid?
嗨 这是什么情况?
Hello? What is this?
我们搭了一个城堡!
We built a fort!
那是我的床单吗?
Are those my sheets?
是啊
Yes, they are.
好吧
Okay.
你们两个幼稚鬼接着玩
Well, you kids have fun.
我要睡了
I'm gonna go to sleep.
Leonard 你不想看看城堡里面是什么样子的吗?
Leonard, don't you want to see the inside of the fort?
不用啦
Yeah, I'm good.
来嘛来嘛
Oh, come on.
我真的好想试试 不许别人进来的感觉
I really wanted to tell someone they can't come in.
好吧
Okay, fine.
Sheldon 我可以参观你的城堡吗?
Sheldon, may I please visit your fort?
我好想说不行啊
I want to say no,
可是这里太棒了 快进来!
but it's too glorious. Get in here!
- 谢了  - 过来 坐在地上
- Thank you.  - Okay, have a seat on the floor.
别坐在那儿 那是我的专座
Not there. That's my spot.